http://www.extension.uci.edu/resources/legal/default.aspx

Your firewall or browser settings may be blocking your ability to submit online payments. If you experience payment problems, please try an alternative enrollment method.
Skip Navigation
Search
Search
Courses
Back
Courses
Course Search
Back
Reading
Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages (TESOL)
TEFL
Engineering
Back
Engineering
Device Software Engineering
Embedded Systems Engineering
Internet of Things
Optics Programs
Facilities Management
NATO Crisis Management and Disaster Response (CMDR)
Water-Energy Nexus
Finance & Accounting
Back
Finance & Accounting
Applied Accounting
Personal Financial Planning
Wealth That Lasts
Healthcare
Tax Information
Trade Adjustment Assistance (TAA)
Veterans Benefits
Workforce Innovation & Opportunity Act (WIOA)
Student Conduct
Back
Student Conduct
Student Conduct
Student Disciplinary Procedures
Student Grievance Procedures
Legal
Back
Legal
Privacy Policy
Students with Disabilities
Non-discrimination
Schedule Changes
Sexual Harassment
FERPA (Student Records)
Other Legal Notices
DCE Alumni Chapter
Back
DCE Alumni Chapter
Coronavirus Updates and Resources
Back
Coronavirus Updates and Resources
About
UCI Open Educational Resources
Massive Open Online Courses (MOOC)
Osher Lifelong Learning Institute (OLLI) at UCI
Concurrent Enrollment
Overview
Registration
Availability/Eligibility
Drops & Refunds
Academic Calendar
General Information
Clear Induction Administrative Services Credential
Gifted & Talented Education (GATE)
Higher Education 101
Independent Educational Consultant
Introductory English
Introductory Mathematics
Montessori Teacher Education Program
Preliminary Administrative Services Credential
Reading
Teaching English as a Foreign Language (TEFL)
Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages (TESOL)
Engineering
Device Software Engineering
Embedded Systems Engineering
Internet of Things: Applications and Opportunities
Optics Programs
Systems Engineering
Environment & Facilities
Emergency Management and Disaster Recovery
Environmental Management
Facilities Management
NATO Crisis Management and Disaster Response (CMDR)
Turfgrass Management Certificate
Water-Energy Nexus
Finance & Accounting
Applied Accounting
CFP® Review
CPA Review
Personal Financial Planning
Personal Financial Planning Accelerated
Clinical Research
Clinical Laboratory Science/Medical Technology (CLS/MT) Training Program
Clinical Trials: Medical Device and Drug Development
Comparative Effectiveness Research and Evidence Based Medicine
Medical Device Development
Post-Baccalaureate Premedical Program
Post-Baccalaureate Program in Pharmaceutical Sciences
Regulatory Affairs and Compliance
Technology
Agile Project Management.
Blockchain Technologies
Business Intelligence & Data Warehousing
Computer Programming Courses
Cyber Security
Data Analytics for Business
Data Science
Database Management
Full Stack Web Development
Java Programming
Machine and Deep Learning
Mobile Application Development
Predictive Analytics
Python for Data Science, Web and Core Programming
Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
Web Design
Web Intelligence
International
Corporate Education
Overview
Global Leadership Program
Learning Consortium: Short Courses
UCI &plus Jolt: Micro-Courses
Tax Information
Trade Adjustment Assistance (TAA)
Veterans Benefits
Workforce Innovation & Opportunity Act (WIOA)
Student Conduct
Code of Conduct
Netiquette
Academic Honesty
Student Disciplinary Procedures
Student Grievance Procedures
Legal Information
Privacy Policy
Students with Disabilities
Non-discrimination
Schedule Changes
Sexual Harassment
FERPA (Student Records)
Other Legal Notices
DCE Alumni Chapter
About
UCI Continuing Education
Mission, Vision, Core Values
Dean Gary Matkin
Press Releases
Trending Now
Privacy Policy
We haven't noticed any activity for minutes.
Would you like to refresh your session?
Time remaining:
Your session has timed out.
Would you like to restart your session?
Privacy Policy
Students with Disabilities
Non-discrimination
Schedule Changes
Sexual Harassment
FERPA (Student Records)
Other Legal Notices
Overview
Your privacy is very important to us. UCI Division of Continuing Education is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. We support the Fair Information Practices defined by the U.S. government and privacy initiatives in other countries.
We do not release your personal data with any third party outside the UCI Division of Continuing Education: we do not and will never sell, rent or share your name, mailing address, email address or any other data that can personally identify you in any way to any outside group.
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the UCI Division of Continuing Education Web site following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes
Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998
UCI Division of Continuing Education abides by the provisions of the federal Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA), which requires prompt response to claims of copyright infringement by copyright holders or their agents. If the campus receives an allegation of copyright infringement based on your use of the UCI network via an IP address assigned to you, the matter is assigned to the Student Life & Leadership Office (Dean of Students) and UCI Division of Continuing Education’s Office of the Registrar for further investigation. If you have questions about the DMCA, please contact UCI Division of Continuing Education’s Student Services Unit/Office of the Registrar at (949) 824-5414 or via e-mail at dce-services@uci.edu.
Sending You Information
We send our materials to each of our students and inquiries on a quarterly basis to help you quickly and easily choose the course or program you need for your career success. As you request materials through the web request form, we will rush those materials to you and follow up with other materials of interest to you. At any time, if you wish to be removed from our mailing lists, you may call (949) 824-5414 or send an email to unex@uci.edu and we will be happy to remove you from our contact list as you request. As stated above, we will never make your contact or preference information available to anyone outside of UCI Division of Continuing Education, unless required to do so pursuant to a judicial or governmental order, and even then, only to the extent so ordered.
Links to Other Sites
As a convenience to you, we sometimes provide links to other Web sites. These sites are not under the control of UCI Division of Continuing Education; and the fact that we provide such links is not an indication that UCI Division of Continuing Education endorses or is liable for those sites or their content.
If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at unex@uci.edu.
Social Security Number
By authority of the Regents of the University of California, we ask for your social security number in order to verify your identity for accurate record keeping. Providing the number is voluntary.
Information We Collect
In general, you can visit UCI Division of Continuing Education on the Web without revealing any information about yourself. If you fill out one of our request forms or comment forms, we ask you for information such as your name, address, phone number, and email address so that we may mail you the materials you have requested or so that we may follow up on your comments as you request. In addition, as you register for a class, it is necessary that we collect your full personal data and your credit card information so that we may successfully process your registration and reserve your seat in the course(s) you have requested.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. In that context, you as an individual user remain anonymous.
We may collect and distribute aggregate statistics about our Web site visitors, traffic patterns, and related site information. These statistics do not include information that would allow us or the recipient to identify any individual in any manner whatsoever.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
Data you enter during a visit to our site is stored on systems using the same security standards and procedures that protect our essential business data. Access to your data is restricted to authorized employees for UCI Division of Continuing Education business purposes and based on our employees need to know. Any sensitive or personal data, such as credit card or purchase information, that you enter for online e-commerce transactions, is transmitted in an encrypted form and requires the use of a secure browser. By using the UCI Division of Continuing Education Web site to enter into a credit card transaction, you are consenting to UCI Division of Continuing Education transferring your encrypted credit card information and the dollar amount of the transaction to external companies for credit verification.
Also of Interest
UC Irvine Privacy and Policy Notice
Legal Information
Privacy Policy
Students with Disabilities
Non-discrimination
Schedule Changes
Sexual Harassment
FERPA (Student Records)
Connect with us on:
